# HERBEYG ROBLEDO REYES

## INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ENGINEER

I am a software developer looking to work professionally in the IT area, I will bring my knowledge and commitment to utilize my skills to reach the company's goals. I have 1+ year on experience in development of applications such as videogames and desktop apps. I am looking to enrich and strengthen my knowledge in the IT areas, I am open to practice and improve through new methods and an entire willingness to learn.



## **Work History**

#### 2019-08 -2019-11

## **Software Developer**

#### G-TECH., Durango, Durango

Programmer in the access control system for First Majestic Silver with the purpose of maintaining the security of those who enter the company's facilities, the system was developed in Microsoft Visual Studio using C # as programming language and Microsoft SQL Server to register every access in the database.

#### 2018-10 -2019-07

## **Mobile Game Developer**

#### G-TECH., Durango, Durango

Programmer in the development of hyper casual games for mobile devices with iOS and Android operating system, using object-oriented programming in C # to create the logic and mechanics of the gameplay, in addition to the different modules such as leaderboards and in-app purchases.



# **Internships**

#### 2018-02 -2018-06

## Web Developer

#### Logisti-k de México., San Luis Potosí

Participation in different projects as an analyst, programmer and implementer in the visual design of web platforms. Translation of graphic design into HTML code, using tools such as CSS3 and Bootstrap.

## 2016-05 -2016-08

## **Software Developer**

#### Tribunal Superior de Justiciar del estado de Durango

Programmer in the development and implementation of an automated sending email system for the virtual file of the Superior Court of Justice of the State of Durango, using visual basic to create the program and a database in Microsoft SQL Server to store all the personal data of the litigants, in this way a predefined message is sent at an exact time of day to the corresponding email of the person as a reminder of their next audience.



## **Education**

#### 2016-08 -2018-04

# Bachelor of Engineering Information

Technology

Universidad Tecnológica De Durango - Durango, Durango

### 2014-09 -2016-08

# Associate Degree: Information and Communication Technologies

Universidad Tecnológica De Durango - Durango, Durango



#### Contact

#### **Address**

Street San Rafael #216, Durango, Durango, 34190

#### **Phone**

(+52) 618 139 5843

#### E-mail

HerbeygRobledo@gmail.com



## Languajes

Spanish - Native

English - B2



# Skills

Java

Android

C#

HTML & CSS3

JavaScript

Bootstrap

Microsoft SQL server

MySQL

Git

Unity 2D